[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "How do you manage to do this and why can't more of your colleagues do this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "manage", "to", "do", "this", "and", "why", "ca", "n't", "more", "of", "your", "colleagues", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Respect, affection, traveling together.", "answer_tokens": ["Respect", ",", "affection", ",", "traveling", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Senator Graham, what is the secret to proper bipartisanship, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Senator", "Graham", ",", "what", "is", "the", "secret", "to", "proper", "bipartisanship", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Well, in fairness to our colleagues, Piers, there are a lot of real close friendships around this place.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "fairness", "to", "our", "colleagues", ",", "Piers", ",", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "real", "close", "friendships", "around", "this", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Graham"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Have you ever known him not lose his temper?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "known", "him", "not", "lose", "his", "temper", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "IEBERMAN: Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["IEBERMAN", ":", "Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Or are you comfortable with where things are?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "are", "you", "comfortable", "with", "where", "things", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Actually, I'm comfortable.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "I", "'m", "comfortable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Why aren't there limits on the number of guns and the type of guns?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "n't", "there", "limits", "on", "the", "number", "of", "guns", "and", "the", "type", "of", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, there are limits.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "limits", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "You're going to blame the British?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "going", "to", "blame", "the", "British", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Why do you want eight guns?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "want", "eight", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Because I enjoy shooting.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "enjoy", "shooting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "That argument has gone, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "argument", "has", "gone", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "MD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Where is this deal, in the end, do you think, going to wash up?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "is", "this", "deal", ",", "in", "the", "end", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "going", "to", "wash", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "You know what, the question is whether we have the political will to put the deal together that most people on both sides, both parties will tell you is what has to happen and that is, yes, raise taxes, raise revenues.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "the", "question", "is", "whether", "we", "have", "the", "political", "will", "to", "put", "the", "deal", "together", "that", "most", "people", "on", "both", "sides", ",", "both", "parties", "will", "tell", "you", "is", "what", "has", "to", "happen", "and", "that", "is", ",", "yes", ",", "raise", "taxes", ",", "raise", "revenues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "You've got to be very careful where you encourage the cutting of entitlements, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "got", "to", "be", "very", "careful", "where", "you", "encourage", "the", "cutting", "of", "entitlements", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "RP", ":", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "ORGAN: But why isn't that happening?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "But", "why", "is", "n't", "that", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Don't go out -- don't go out and continue the campaign that is over.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "go", "out", "--", "do", "n't", "go", "out", "and", "continue", "the", "campaign", "that", "is", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "But can you tell me what you saw?", "question_tokens": ["But", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "what", "you", "saw", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Did you see people being escorted out of the mall with their hands in the air?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "people", "being", "escorted", "out", "of", "the", "mall", "with", "their", "hands", "in", "the", "air", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "I didn't see anybody with their hands up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "see", "anybody", "with", "their", "hands", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Santa"]}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Were you close enough to witness any of that?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "close", "enough", "to", "witness", "any", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I did see the Santa stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "see", "the", "Santa", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "What was that scene like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "scene", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "It was horrifying.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "horrifying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "David, there was also another witness that said that people were locked inside the mall, that they were told to stay where they were, but you were able to get out?", "question_tokens": ["David", ",", "there", "was", "also", "another", "witness", "that", "said", "that", "people", "were", "locked", "inside", "the", "mall", ",", "that", "they", "were", "told", "to", "stay", "where", "they", "were", ",", "but", "you", "were", "able", "to", "get", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Do you think it's random?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "random", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Any information about the actual investigation is not going to be appropriate to release right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Any", "information", "about", "the", "actual", "investigation", "is", "not", "going", "to", "be", "appropriate", "to", "release", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Did they do everything they were supposed to in situations like this?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "do", "everything", "they", "were", "supposed", "to", "in", "situations", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "I don't -- I was not here.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "was", "not", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Can you us more about the two victims?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "us", "more", "about", "the", "two", "victims", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "I don't have any identifying information.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "identifying", "information", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Can you confirm that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "confirm", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "I don't have any information about the investigation at this is point that I can share.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "information", "about", "the", "investigation", "at", "this", "is", "point", "that", "I", "can", "share", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Any minor injure?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "minor", "injure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Were you folks in contact with mall security watching it unfold on video camera?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "folks", "in", "contact", "with", "mall", "security", "watching", "it", "unfold", "on", "video", "camera", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I do not have that information.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "not", "have", "that", "information", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "How many people are still in there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "people", "are", "still", "in", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "There's still police officers inside the mall.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "still", "police", "officers", "inside", "the", "mall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["8:00"]}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "And do you expect his name to be released at 8:00?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "expect", "his", "name", "to", "be", "released", "at", "8:00", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I doubt that it will be released at 8:00.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "doubt", "that", "it", "will", "be", "released", "at", "8:00", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["8:00?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "What can you tell us about him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "us", "about", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "It was an adult male.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "an", "adult", "male", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Was he 20S, 30s, 40s?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "20S", ",", "30s", ",", "40s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "That's the extent of the information I've been given.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "extent", "of", "the", "information", "I", "'ve", "been", "given", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Was he wearing a mask?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "wearing", "a", "mask", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "I don't have that information for you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "that", "information", "for", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Were any shots fired outside the mall?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "any", "shots", "fired", "outside", "the", "mall", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I'm --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Did the shooter shoot anybody outside the mall?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "the", "shooter", "shoot", "anybody", "outside", "the", "mall", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "I don't have any information about the shooter to share with anybody.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "information", "about", "the", "shooter", "to", "share", "with", "anybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Has law enforcement identified the shooter?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "law", "enforcement", "identified", "the", "shooter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I do not know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "not", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Do you think that younger people don't care nearly as much about it as their parents and grandparents?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "younger", "people", "do", "n't", "care", "nearly", "as", "much", "about", "it", "as", "their", "parents", "and", "grandparents", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I think part of it's generational.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "part", "of", "it", "'s", "generational", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 551, "question": "But can they both be equal?", "question_tokens": ["But", "can", "they", "both", "be", "equal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "DT", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "RAHAM: Well, here's what --", "answer_tokens": ["RAHAM", ":", "Well", ",", "here", "'s", "what", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Can I answer this?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "answer", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "What do you think they should decide?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "they", "should", "decide", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I -- I think that marriage ought to be decided by the states.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "think", "that", "marriage", "ought", "to", "be", "decided", "by", "the", "states", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Well, is it possible for three people to genuinely love each other and want to share their lives together?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "is", "it", "possible", "for", "three", "people", "to", "genuinely", "love", "each", "other", "and", "want", "to", "share", "their", "lives", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Of course it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "OK, then, is it OK to have three people marry each other?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "then", ",", "is", "it", "OK", "to", "have", "three", "people", "marry", "each", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Uh, I would say not.", "answer_tokens": ["Uh", ",", "I", "would", "say", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Because the point is simply a homosexual couple's right to get married in the same way as the heterosexual couple in America.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "the", "point", "is", "simply", "a", "homosexual", "couple", "'s", "right", "to", "get", "married", "in", "the", "same", "way", "as", "the", "heterosexual", "couple", "in", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Would you allow slavery in some states but not others?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "allow", "slavery", "in", "some", "states", "but", "not", "others", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "You know what we're dealing with --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "we", "'re", "dealing", "with", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "And very quickly on pot, are you in favor of legalizing pot?", "question_tokens": ["And", "very", "quickly", "on", "pot", ",", "are", "you", "in", "favor", "of", "legalizing", "pot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "What the experts tell me, at least the ones I've talked to, it's really a gateway drug that may lead to more drug addiction.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "the", "experts", "tell", "me", ",", "at", "least", "the", "ones", "I", "'ve", "talked", "to", ",", "it", "'s", "really", "a", "gateway", "drug", "that", "may", "lead", "to", "more", "drug", "addiction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "-- have you ever inhaled?", "question_tokens": ["--", "have", "you", "ever", "inhaled", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "RAHAM: No.", "answer_tokens": ["RAHAM", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "-- just to find out?", "question_tokens": ["--", "just", "to", "find", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "-- I don't -- I don't pretend to be normal.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "pretend", "to", "be", "normal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "How abnormal are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "abnormal", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "At the end of the day, I -- I -- I want to be me.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", ",", "I", "--", "I", "--", "I", "want", "to", "be", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "What would you most like, politically, as a gift?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "most", "like", ",", "politically", ",", "as", "a", "gift", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RBS", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Obviously, I think all of us, and all Americans, a resolution of this issue of the fiscal cliff so that people can live next year with a sense of predictability, with a sense that they are going to have a growing economy, and, frankly, peace in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["Obviously", ",", "I", "think", "all", "of", "us", ",", "and", "all", "Americans", ",", "a", "resolution", "of", "this", "issue", "of", "the", "fiscal", "cliff", "so", "that", "people", "can", "live", "next", "year", "with", "a", "sense", "of", "predictability", ",", "with", "a", "sense", "that", "they", "are", "going", "to", "have", "a", "growing", "economy", ",", "and", ",", "frankly", ",", "peace", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "And a place on this committee?", "question_tokens": ["And", "a", "place", "on", "this", "committee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Oh, I -- I think it would be fun to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "--", "I", "think", "it", "would", "be", "fun", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hanukah"]}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Senator Lieberman?", "question_tokens": ["Senator", "Lieberman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Christmas and Hanukah.", "answer_tokens": ["Christmas", "and", "Hanukah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lieberman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "So, uh, what -- what would I really like from the president?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "uh", ",", "what", "--", "what", "would", "I", "really", "like", "from", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "Senator Graham?", "question_tokens": ["Senator", "Graham", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "Three things.", "answer_tokens": ["Three", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Graham"]}}]